UNITE HERE Local 169 Files 6200/001
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- New School grievance case: Termination, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 125)
- New School grievance case: Settlement, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 126)
- New School grievance case: Termination Off Post 1/6/06, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 127)
- New School grievance case: Arbitration 1/25/06 Notes and Summation, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 128)
- New School grievance case, 2003-2006 (Box 4, Folder 129)
- New School grievance case: Cont'd, 2004-2005 (Box 4, Folder 130)
- New School grievance case: Termination 9/29/04, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 131)
  1st forms
- New School grievance case: Responses Etc., 2005 (Box 4, Folder 132)
- UNITE Benefits Conference, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- UNITE Health & Welfare Summary Plan Description Leaflets (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Leaflet UNITE for Workplace Headaches (Box 5, Folder 3)
- UNITE - Textiles and Much, Much More! (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Gallery 169 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Local 169 Political Action Committee, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Constitutions - International and Local, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Press Lists (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Local 168 Executive Council Meeting, 2001-2002 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- NYC Central Labor Council - Labor Community Advocacy, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Hotel - Laundries, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Targets - NYC Retail (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Made in New York City Campaign, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Internet Search Engine Info, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Arts & Letter (Executive Accessories), 2001 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Organizing Plan, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- NSU Correspondence - Greggory Spence (Box 5, Folder 17)
  empty folder
- Tour 1, 2004-2005 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Tour II (Box 5, Folder 19)
  Empty folder
- Tour III (Box 5, Folder 20)
  Empty Folder
- Mandatory OT List (Stuck List), 2004-2005 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Birds Eye - 10K, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Interface Solutions, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Allied One Solution, 2004-2005 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- SEIU/New School CBA Hi-Lites, 2006-2007 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Local 169 - New School Side Letter on Absenteeism, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Amalg NE Joint Board Minutes - Kevin Finnegan (Box 5, Folder 27)
- 24 diskettes (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Buttons and Print Blocks, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  6 UNITE Local 169 button, 9 portrait blocks, 1 group photo block, 1 White House letter block